[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "Janet, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "I'm very giddy right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 17, "question": "Giddy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 18, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 23, "question": "How do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 24, "answer": "I'm not very keen about doing interviews.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 25, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 26, "answer": "I'm not much of a talker.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 36, "question": "Which one have I got today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 37, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "You are two people, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "Three or four?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Say you're 3 or 4.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Would you take that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, there were two things that I wanted.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Did you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "If you had that power again not to be famous, would you prefer not to be or do you quite like it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "I don't mind it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Isn't it skull and cross bones?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NNS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Is this -- what are they, the heads of interviewers who've disappointed you over the years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "I told you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "Which one is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "It's this one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Sort of creepy, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "How many skull-like things do you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Oh, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "She did the whole week?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "She was laughing but it was just ridiculous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "What would you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "It's bingeing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "ORGAN: Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "What made you suddenly think I've got to get a grip?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "It's been a few times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "How depressed did you get?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "There was -- it was pretty bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "ORGAN: What's \"pretty bad\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "``", "RB", "JJ", "''", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "It depends.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Michael called you Donk, didn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael", "Donk"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Do you think in your case it affected you more than any of them realized, that it was all chipping away at your self-esteem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 266, "question": "Hard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 267, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 273, "question": "What were you thinking when you did that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "I --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 275, "question": "Crazy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 276, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "Did you ever feel suicidal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Everyone has it, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "What kind of things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "I hear about -- OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "People do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "How would you position him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "I think my father means well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "How old were you then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "I was very young.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Does he -- does he ever tell you that he loves you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Yes, he has.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "He has that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "He has done that before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Well, you think I'm going to sit here and lie to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Maybe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "When did you last talk to him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Honestly it's not often.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "JJ", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "Months?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "It's been -- oh, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 422, "question": "Do you feel sad you don't have a relationship with him that is better?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBZ", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 423, "answer": "Not anymore.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "What did you call him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Joseph.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "And what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "He said no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Do you think you'll have children?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "I hope so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Do you worry the clock is ticking or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jermaine Dupree"]}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Have you come close to thinking right, I'm going to have a baby now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "TO", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "I never really thought about having children until I got with Jermaine Dupree, when he and I were together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Don't you -- be a good mom?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", ":", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "I hope so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "What would you do differently if you had a child to the way your father treated you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "A lot of attention.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 494, "question": "Do you feel he smiles down on you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 495, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "The kid?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "When you came along and you became his back watcher, and you both got a little bit older each time, how did your relationship evolve?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "We were very close.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Have you got to that stage yet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "What do you think about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "About passing out the dinners to the homeless.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "What was the misconceptions of Michael, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Very sweet.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Do you think most people misunderstood him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "NNS", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "DT", ":", "DT", "CD", "IN", "CD", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "JJ", ":", "CD", "IN", "CD", "CC", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Is it that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "This -- this -- this one on one it's just -- even -- one on one or are getting in front of a small group, that's difficult for me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "Isn't that weird?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "It is weird.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "IN", "POS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Isn't that crazy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "I mean, I can't -- I don't know what that's like because I've never done that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "WP", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "Where do you want to start?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "You're the one who wants to talk about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "Am I?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "Well yes, they're a bit more prudish in America, aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "It could be, couldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Possibly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "No, truly in love five.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 660, "question": "How come it just went from three to five?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "TO", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 661, "answer": "Because I wasn't --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "You high maintenance, low maintenance, middle maintenance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "I always thought I was low maintenance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 676, "question": "What?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "Your extensive entourage, it appears to suggest that maybe --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "Extensive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "-- middling to high.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "Is it that bad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "It's not that bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Have you -- have you ever been a diva?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 696, "question": "Well, which one did you mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WDT", "CD", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 697, "answer": "LaToya.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "She loves being a diva, doesn't she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "I mean, she's beautiful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "What went wrong there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "Oh, I can't speak about it, unfortunately.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "Oh, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 750, "question": "Are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 751, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RBR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "I've got skulls everywhere, see?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "You have -- you've got even more skulls.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 764, "question": "I mean it's a bit weird, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 765, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "You say you like them, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "Yes, but you talk about love and everything and then you're just covered in skulls.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 772, "question": "But what's wrong with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 773, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 779, "question": "I don't -- to you, do I have an accent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 780, "answer": "Of course you do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 781, "question": "I do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "ORGAN: Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 787, "question": "If I wanted to make you really happy, how would I do it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 788, "answer": "I don't know if you could.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 795, "question": "Are you excited?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 796, "answer": "I'm so excited.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110215pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 803, "question": "What's been the best moment of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 804, "answer": "It would have to be a moment that I'm not going to go into but a moment with my family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]